const quizData = [
    {
        number: "1",
        question: "What is my favourite ice cream flavour",
        answers: ["Chocolate","Green Tea","Mint Chocolate Chip","Mango"],
        correctAnswer:"Green Tea",
        src: "iceCream"
    },
    {
        number: "2",
        question: "Where was I born",
        answers: ["Canada","Hong Kong","Malaysia","China"],
        correctAnswer:"Canada",
        src:"btsFlag"

    },

    {
        number: "3",
        question: "When is my birthday?",
        answers: ["June 19th","June 18th","June 27th","June 29th"],
        correctAnswer:"June 19th",
        src:"catBirthday"
    },
    {
        number: "4",
        question: "Where did we go on our first date?",
        answers: ["A park","Movie theatre","Art gallery","Restaurant"],
        correctAnswer:"Movie theatre",
        src:"catLove"
    },
    {
        number: "5",
        question: "What is my favourite fast food restaurant?",
        answers: ["McDonalds","Harveys","Wendys","Jolibee"],
        correctAnswer:"Wendys",
        src:"fatCat"
    },
    {
        number: "6",
        question: "What is my favourite pop drink?",
        answers: ["Coke","Iced Tea","Sprite","Fruitopia"],
        correctAnswer:"Iced Tea",
        src:"catDrinking"
    },
    {
        number: "7",
        question: "What is my favourite song?",
        answers: ["One More Love Song","Baby Blue","The Place Where He Inserted The Blade","Laundry"],
        correctAnswer:"One More Love Song",
        src:"catMusic"
    },
    {
        number: "7",
        question: "Results Page",
        answers: ["Next"],
        correctAnswer:"",
        src:"goodJob"
    },
    {
        question: "Ready for a bonus question?",
        answers: ["Yes"],
    },
    {
        question: "Well...",
        answers: ["Yes?"],

    },
    {
        question: "Um...",
        answers: ["What"],

    },
    {
        question: "Can I ask you something?",
        answers: ["Yes"],

    },
    {
        question: "...",
        answers: ["?"],

    },
    {
        question: "Well...",
        answers: ["???"],

    },
    {
        question: "...",
        answers: ["?"],

    },
    {
        number: "7",
        question: "Want to play brawl?",
        answers: ["WTF"],
        src:"brawlKiss"
    },
    {
        number: "7",
        question: "Just kidding.",
        answers: ["Okay, then what?"],
        src:"goofyEmoji"
    },
    {
        question: "Well...",
        answers: ["???"],

    },
    {
        number: "7",
        question: "Will you be my valentine?",
        src:"pixelHeart",
        answers: ["Yes","Super Yes"],
    },
    {
        number: "7",
        question: "YIPEEEEEEEEE!!!!!!! <3 <3 <3",
        answers: [],
        src:"yipee"
    }

    
]
export default quizData;